Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979-2014; 7; 10.5 cubic ft.
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - The Record, 2008 (Oversized 5, Folder 1)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Buzz News Clippings, 2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 1)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 2)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 3)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 4)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 5)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 6)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 2000s (Oversized 6, Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2010-2011 (Oversized 7, Folder 1)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, 2011 (Oversized 7, Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2012 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2013 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Times Union News Clippings, 2014 (Oversized 7, Folder 3)
  - Times Union News Clippings, 2014 (Oversized 7, Folder 4)
  - Times Union News Clippings, 2014 (Oversized 7, Folder 5)
  - Times Union News Clippings, 2014 (Oversized 7, Folder 6)
  - New York Times-Men's Lacorsse, 2014 (Oversized 7, Folder 7)
  - Golf News Clippings, Undated (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
- Scrapbooks, 1940-1996; 8; 9.5 cubic ft.
  Contains scrapbooks of assorted photographs and newspaper clippings.
  - Basketball, Baseball, Football, Intramural, 1940-1941 (Oversized 1, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1955-1956 (Oversized 1, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1956-1957 (Oversized 1, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1957-1958 (Oversized 1, Item 4)
  - Basketball, 1958-1959 (Oversized 1, Item 5)
  - Basketball, 1959-1960 (Oversized 1, Item 6)
  - Basketball, 1960-1961 (Oversized 2, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1961-1962 (Oversized 2, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1962-1963 (Oversized 2, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1963-1964 (Oversized 2, Item 4)
  - Women's Tennis, 1964-1965 (Oversized 2, Item 5)
  - Basketball, Wrestling, 1964-1965 (Oversized 2, Item 6)
  - Basketball, 1966-1967 (Oversized 3, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1967-1968 (Oversized 3, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1968-1969 (Oversized 3, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1969-1970 (Oversized 3, Item 4)
  - Basketball, 1970-1971 (Oversized 3, Item 5)
  - Basketball, 1971-1972 (Oversized 3, Item 6)
  - Football, 1971-1972 (Oversized 4, Item 1)
  - Baskeball, 1972-1973 (Oversized 4, Item 2)
  - Football, 1973 (Oversized 4, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1973-1974 (Oversized 4, Item 4)
  - Football, 1974 (Oversized 4, Item 5)
  - Basketball, 1974-1975 (Oversized 5, Item 1)
  - Football, 1975 (Oversized 5, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1975-1976 (Oversized 5, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1976-1977 (Oversized 5, Item 4)
  - Football, 1977 (Oversized 5, Item 5)
  - Basketball, 1977-1978 (Oversized 6, Item 1)
  - Football, 1978 (Oversized 6, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1978-1979 (Oversized 6, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1980-1981 (Oversized 6, Item 4)
  - Football, 1981 (Oversized 7, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1981-1982 (Oversized 7, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1982-1983 (Oversized 7, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1983-1984 (Oversized 7, Item 4)
  - Basketball, 1984-1985 (Oversized 7, Item 5)
  - Football, 1985-1986 (Oversized 8, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1985-1986 (Oversized 8, Item 2)
  - Basketballl, 1986-1987 (Oversized 8, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1988-1989 (Oversized 9, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1989-1990 (Oversized 9, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1990-1991 (Oversized 9, Item 3)
  - Basketball, 1991-1992 (Oversized 9, Item 4)
  - Basketball, 1992-1993 (Oversized 10, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1993-1994 (Oversized 10, Item 2)
  - Basketball, 1994-1995 (Oversized 11, Item 1)
  - Basketball, 1995-1996 (Oversized 11, Item 2)
- Photographs, 1955-2014; 9; 12.5 cubic ft.
  Contains photographs of UAlbany student-athletes.
  - Jim Oppedisano, 1955-1956 team, Dennis Johnson, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Athletics, Awards 1950's Awards Ceremony, ca. 1950 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Team Photo- Men's Basketball, ca. 1950-ca. 1960 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - AA Board All Sports Banquet, 1968 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - AA Board Banquet Photograph, 1968 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, 1969 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Football Photo Plaques, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Football Photo Plaques, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Football Photo Plaques, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Football Photo Plaques, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Football Photo Plaques, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Lacrosse Against Siena, 1971 May (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Football, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Football Headshots, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Football Misc, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Football Team Photo, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Football Team Photo, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Football Team Photo, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Football Team Photo, ca. 1970-ca. 1980 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football, ca. 1970; ca. 1980; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Football Headshots, ca. 1970; ca. 1980; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Football Misc., ca. 1970; ca. 1980; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Football Misc., ca. 1970; ca. 1980; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Football Staff, ca. 1970; ca. 1980; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Albany State Coaches Reunion, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Football, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Football Misc., 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Football, ca. 1980-ca. 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1980-ca. 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball and Football- Slides and Negatives, ca. 1980-ca. 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball- Team Photos, ca. 1980-ca. 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball- Team Photos, ca. 1980-ca. 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Football Team Photo, 1990 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Football Negatives, 1993 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Press Conference, R.A.C.C. Special Olympics, 1993 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Div. II Press Conference/NECC, 1994 May 16 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Football, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Baseball, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Football, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Men's + Rack and Field, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Women's Softball, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Women's Tennis, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Women's Volleyball, 1995 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball- Team Photos, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Field Hockey, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Men's Soccer, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Volleyball, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Women's Soccer, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Baseball, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Baseball-Photographs and Schedule, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Field Hockey, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Football, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Men's Basketball, Doc Savers, Daredevils, D. Foire, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Men's Basketball Negatives, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Men's Soccer, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Men's Track and Field, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Track and Field, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Volleyball, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Women's Soccer, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Women's Soccer, 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Scott Beeten and Coaches, ca. 1997 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Coach Hicks- 1997-1998 Men's Basketball Team (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Football, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Football, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Football, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Women's Tennis, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Field Hockey, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Football, 1997-1999 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Softball, 1997-1999 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Football, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football Captains, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Football- Team Photo, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball [Slides], 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Men's Soccer, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Softball, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Tennis, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Track and Field, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Volleyball, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Women's Soccer, 1998 (Box 3 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Football Hall of Fame, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Football Hall of Fame, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Football Hall of Fame, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Men's Soccer, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Softball, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball, ca. 1998 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Football Team Photo, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Women's Soccer, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Baseball, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Field Hockey, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Field Hockey-with Negatives, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Football [Slides], 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Football, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Men's and Women's Track and Field, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Men's Baseball and Lacrosse, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball #10F2, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Men's Soccer, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Softball, 1999 (Box 4 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Volleyball, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Women's Field Hockey, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, ca. 1999 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Athletics Book Photo, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Community Service, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball-Headshots, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Track and Field, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball (NEGS), 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - W. Basketball Ann Aldrich, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - W. Basketball Cara Caffell, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - W. Basketball Chris Gray, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - W. Basketball Dawn Dimicco, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - W. Basketball Head Shots, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - W. Basketball Jess McGinLay, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - W. Basketball Lauren O'Brien, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - W. Basketball Liz Tucker, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - W. Basketball Mallana Wheelwright, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - W. Basketball Marie Connors, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - W. Basketball Mari Warner, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - W. Basketball Megan Buchanan, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - W. Basketball Melissa Schoonover, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Women's Basketball Misc, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Women's Field Hockey, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Women's Tennis, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Women's Tennis, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Bob Ford, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Baseball Pictures-with Disc, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Dr. Marinello, Alfred, Alley, Striken, Shawkardas, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Field Hockey, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Football, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Football, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Football, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Football Bob Ewell Photography, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 5 (9-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Football-Bob Ewell Photography, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Football Coaching Staff, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Football Letterwinners, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Football, negatives, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Football, negatives, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Hall of Fame-Pat Ryder, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Headshots and Slides-Various Sports, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Hoops Negatives, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball Headshots, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Men's Lacrosse, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Ualbany Athletics, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - University Administration-Dr. Hitchcock, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - University At Albany, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Wofx Radio, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Year-By-Year Results, ca. 1999-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, 1999-2003 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Football Slides, 1999; 2000; Undated (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Athletics Facility, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Athletic Staff Golfing, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Faculty Golfing, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Men's Track and Field, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Giants-Summer Training Camp [3.5 in floppy], ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Men's Track and Field, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Negatives, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Photos from Publications, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Women's Basketball, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Women's Basketball, 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Women's Basketball, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Women's Basketball-Team Photo, ca. 1990 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Football and Basketball headshots, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Football and Basketball Headshots, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Joe Rajczak, Joe Savino, Rafaela Nikas, Dan Gmelin, Dr. Richard Hall, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Headshots, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 6 (9-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball Headshots-Negatives, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball Staff, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Men's Soccer, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Men's Lacrosse, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Men's Soccer, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball Social Event, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Women's Tennis, ca. 1990-ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Baseball, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Baseball Mike Ruebler, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Columbia Basketball Pre-Game Alumni Party, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Giants [co], 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Lacrosse [3.5 in floppy], 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Women's Field Hockey Players, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Track and Field- with Tammy Freeman, ca. 2000 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Athletics [3.5 in floppy], 2000-2001 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Basketball Negatives, 2000-2001 (Box 7 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Headshots, 2000-2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball Part 1, 2000-2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Part 2, 2000-2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Brian DePasquale Asst. Director For Media Relations- Athletic Inserts, 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Field Hockey (cd), 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Football [CD], 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [CD], 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball- Purple Growl, 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Softball, 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Track and Field Negatives [CD], 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Volleyball[CD], 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Women's Soccer [CD], 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Baseball, ca. 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Baseball, ca. 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Football [CD], ca. 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Men's Lacrosse, ca. 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Track and field, ca. 2001 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball [CD], 2001-2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football Staff Photos, ca. 2001-2009 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Football Team Photos, 2001-2011 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Field Hockey, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)